I'm 24.
Really?
You don't even look like the same person.
She caught me making out with you.
I was like, "What the hell?
Why is there a gap here?
Hey, welcome.
Welcome.
Hello.
Oh, my God, you two are adorable.
Reserve seats, please.
Here you go, sir. Here you go.
Today's special reserve seat guests.
Rika Shimakura and Mio Hirai from BEYOND!
Seino.
I'm BEYOND!
I'm Rika Shimakura.
I'm Mio Hirai.
Pleased to meet you.
As usual.
BEYOND celebration.
BEYOND.
The group's name comes from the English word BEYOND.
It means "beyond what is beyond".
We want to go beyond the existing framework to the future freely.
We hope that the group will grow and expand into the future freely beyond the existing framework.
We are a combined group of Subway, Rain Forest, Kawao, and Seasonings.
We aim to create a slime-like group that can transform itself into any shape.
We are aiming to be a group like a slime that can change its shape at will.
And that's why we're here for the second time, isn't it?
As for the BEYOND Tomorrows...
We had a different member come before.
Last time, Kiyo's Monhime and Egtsu Sayaka were here.
Let's meet them.
It's hard to come to an adult bar like this, isn't it?
It's not like a bunch of kids came here.
But I'm around Theory.
How old do I look?
I thought I was 16 or 17.
But I'm glad.
Not at all?
I'm still embarrassed.
How old are you, Rika?
Twenty-three.
Twenty-three?
You're a grown-up!
Kokoro is?
I'm 21.
No, you're not 21.
And I'm 24.
Really?
You can't see it.
Yes, it's a trick. It's a trick. It's a trick.
I've introduced you in the café before.
Rika Shimakura loves Showa-era songs.
What kind of Showa songs do you like?
Well, I originally loved Seiko Matsuda, so I started listening to idols.
Keiichi Ota and Akira Terao.
You heard your parents listening to them and thought they were good?
I fell in love with them on my own. It was like we shared a hobby.
I'd tell them how much I missed them, and they'd tell me about them.
Do you sing karaoke together?
I go to karaoke with my father.
We take turns singing only Showa songs.
That's great. It's so much fun.
What is your favorite Seiko song, Pearl?
There are many, but I like Blue Photograph, Seifuku, Eighteen...
You're all in austere clothes.
Not the kind of titles that would appear in the main program.
That's right.
What about Ryo Terawaki?
Ryo Terawaki is a wanderer, on loan...
Wanderer?
But there was an A side and a B side back then, right?
I didn't know that.
I've been listening to it since I was quite late.
I'm listening to the album songs.
I'm listening to it regardless of A side or B side.
So it doesn't matter which one was cut into a single or not?
Yes, it does.
That's why I think I know some songs
I think that's why I know some of the less famous songs.
What else?
Let's see... Teresaten.
And recently, I'm really into Juicy Fruit.
I'm really into them.
Juicy Fruit.
I was caught making out with you.
Version.
You're staring right back at me.
Why is there a gap here?
Ms. Hirai told me that her second photo book, Believe, came out in April.
I spent 5 months working on my body for my second photo book.
You did a body makeover?
Yes, and the staff who knew the process put it together for me.
But I also did it by eating right, going to the gym, going for a walk every morning, fasting for a short period of time, etc.
He is really stoic.
You didn't bring it today?
I did.
Yay!
Let's see how you look now that you've made up your body.
Okay, den den den den.
Oh, that's cool.
I'm a little embarrassed to show you this.
I've also signed it.
I'll get it later.
You don't even look like the same person.
He's so different, isn't he?
They are so different.
I have a favorite cut.
You worked on your back muscles a lot this time, didn't you?
Back muscles
Here it is.
Wow, so cool!
So cool!
It's the same person, in case you were wondering.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The gap is burning. The gap is burning.
I hope you'll have a chance to see it later.
May I have a moment? Oh, by all means.
I haven't seen it on TV.
I haven't seen it on TV either. It's not much to look at.
It's so cool! It's so cool!
I had a lot of input on the costumes and places I wanted to shoot this time.
I think it turned out to be a book that is a little bit like me.
Uniquely me?
See? Did you see it? What was your favorite one? The one with the baby in the loungewear.
Yeah, there's something about it. It's so cute.
Embarrassing. You did a great job.
This is going to sell like hotcakes.
It's got a DVD, too. The making of.
How much for this?
How much is this?
3,182 yen, plus tax.
Plus tax.
3,182 yen plus tax.
I hope you'll all buy it.
I hope you'll buy it.
Thank you very much!
Now then, let's go to the cafe known as Max Talk!
Here is the BEYOND Max Talk!
There's a dinosaur I'd like to meet.
What? Who is this?
Who's this?
I know, right?
What? What kind of dinosaur do you like?
Parasaurolophus.
Giganotosaurus.
Argentinosaurus.
Furaptor, and so on and so forth.
You're laughing.
I was just thinking that we don't seem to be on the same page.
That's a little difficult.
I've never heard of it.
We just met so suddenly.
We were talking about the Showa era, and suddenly I feel like you're distancing yourself.
No, it's just that he's fascinating.
I'd like to meet the dinosaurs.
Meet up?
You can't meet him, can you? Maybe we can.
You don't go to places like Tyrannosaurus, do you?
Of course I like them, but I've selected four that I'd like to get to know better.
I selected four of them. They all have different characteristics.
They are different.
You don't know what kind of dinosaurs they are.
I do.
illustrated them for you, so you can get an idea of what they look like.
Here's the first one.
Parasaralolophus.
Oh, I think I've seen this one before.
I think I've seen something like that before.
This one's famous.
I'm here, I'm here.
It looks like a very strange creature.
But this is what makes it so special.
It extends several meters.
There's a very long tube here.
That's where it makes its sound.
Isn't it cute?
I don't know if this looks like the real thing.
It looks exactly like the real thing.
It's just like the real thing.
It's been in some famous movies.
Oh, yes, yes.
It's in a movie. - No, it's not.
No, it's not.
I just did.
Did you see it? There it is.
Yes, it's here.
Not the main one.
They're herbivores.
Herbivores.
And then...
Giganotosaurus.
I don't know... I don't know...
Do they look alike or not?
They look exactly alike.
Giganotosaurus
Giganotosaurus...
You mentioned Tyrannosaurus earlier.
It's a colonial dinosaur, bigger than a tyrannosaurus.
Bigger?
Bigger.
I thought Tyrannosaurus was the max.
No, it's got the word "giga" in it.
It's a big dinosaur.
It's big, but its hands are tiny.
I think that's cute and I like it.
Isn't Frangerson tiny?
Yes, they are tiny. Isn't it cute?
I love the name Giganotosaurus, and I think it's cool.
Why do you think it's cool?
I mean, it's cool, but doesn't it mean something?
Giga means big.
Isn't that a bit rough?
I like the name.
Especially this one.
Dinosaurs have strange names, don't they?
Yes, they do.
Do you have one of these?
It is Fukui Raptor, as I mentioned earlier.
This is a dinosaur discovered in Fukui.
It is very famous. There are many dinosaurs displayed in front of the station.
Yes, it is.
I didn't know this.
Is there one? Really?
He looks like a model.
This is totally different.
What? It's not the same.
Not at all. She doesn't look exactly the same.
Your legs look a little better.
That's why you're the guy in front of the station.
You've got beautiful legs.
That's right. They're sometimes named after places.
That's why it's called Futaba Suzuki School, and the one Mr. Suzuki found in Futaba County in Fukushima is called Futaba Suzuki School.
It even has a name?
Yes, there used to be a movie about a dinosaur that grew up in Doraemon, and I used to like it so much that I went to see the bones.
Even now, there are excavation sites and places where children can do things like that.
Why do I like dinosaurs?
They're not here anymore, but they were here hundreds of millions of years ago, right where we live, and I think that's really romantic.
They actually walked here, and that's not a fantasy at all.
It's not a fantasy at all.
I think it's amazing to be able to see the bones and stuff that are still there.
There are still traces of it, right?
That's right.
That's why they reconstruct dinosaurs and so on.
But every year new discoveries are made.
Yes, yes, they used to have hair.
And the Thyarzaeus didn't used to have feathers on their backs.
But now we know it has wings.
And then we started to know its color...
Yes, yes.
They've made all kinds of discoveries.
Now we're getting on the same page.
I want to talk about it some more.
Is there more?
Yes, ma'am.
Argentinosaurus.
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm not kidding.
Argentinosaurus.
He's a big guy.
The only thing it says is "big neck".
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I thought it might help you understand.
I like this one.
Yes, I do.
That's why they're in the sea, and they're in the sky, and some of them live on land.
Some of them live on land... and that's the strangest thing about all of this... it's the same planet.
No, it's the strangest thing of all. And here's another song I want you to listen to...
AAA's single "High to Diamond Go City" is the law of hooks, and today I'd like to introduce the song "High to Diamond" from the AAA single "High to Diamond Go City".
High to Diamond
You know, Momohime-chan was playing in the intro of that song.
That's a talkbox instrument.
The keys are connected to a hose.
The sound played on the keyboard goes through the hose and is added to the mouth.
The sound comes out from inside of the mouth, and by changing the shape of the mouth
by changing the shape of the mouth.
By changing the shape of the mouth.
What's that? That's strange.
It's very difficult to play.
It's not an old instrument, is it?
But I hear there are a lot of them.
Momohime is the first idol to play it.
It's used in a lot of Western music.
There are three A-sides on one CD.
That's right.
So you're saying there are three sides to a CD?
That's how it is.
So you're the new principal of Harpol, right?
Yes.
The chorus is called "Doubleshy Melody.
What's it called?
There's an upper part and a lower part.
Both parts are the main part of the song.
And there's also a humming melody all the way through the song.
The song and dance are quite challenging.
I hope you will pay attention to those parts.
Thank you very much.
You look so cool!
You guys have a totally different vibe.
I can't believe it!
It's so danceable!
Please subscribe to our channel!